[
  {
    "question":"When Samson killed 1000 Philistines at Lehi what weapon did he use?",
    "correctOption":"Jawbone of an ass",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Stick",
    "secondOption": "Jawbone of an ass",
    "thirdOption": "A sword",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How old (years) was David when he was anointed King of Israel?",
    "correctOption":"30",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "30",
    "secondOption": "20",
    "thirdOption": "40",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Aside from Peter and John, which disciple witnessed Jesus’ Transfiguration?",
    "correctOption":"James",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Andrew",
    "secondOption": "Judas",
    "thirdOption": "James",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"In Damascus, whose sight was restored by Ananias?",
    "correctOption":"Saul",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Saul",
    "secondOption": "Peter",
    "thirdOption": "Bartimaeus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How many rivers were formed from the river that went out of Eden?",
    "correctOption":"4",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "4",
    "secondOption": "3",
    "thirdOption": "6",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of the place where Jacob slept and dreamed of Jacob's Ladder?",
    "correctOption":"Bethel",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Bethel",
    "secondOption": "Moriah",
    "thirdOption": "Land of Mantle",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who told Naaman to wash in the river Jordan 7 times in order to cure his leprosy?",
    "correctOption":"Elisha",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Elisha",
    "secondOption": "Elisha Servant",
    "thirdOption": "Elijah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who announced to Zachariah that his wife would bear a child to be named John the Baptist?",
    "correctOption":"Angel Gabriel",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Angel Gabriel",
    "secondOption": "Angel Raphael",
    "thirdOption": "Angel Micheal",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who said, 'as for me and my house, we will serve the Lord'?",
    "correctOption":"Joshua",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Naomi",
    "secondOption": "Joshua",
    "thirdOption": "Ruth",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"God tested Abraham by telling him to offer his only son as a burnt offering. Who was that son?",
    "correctOption":"Isaac",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Ishmael",
    "secondOption": "Abram",
    "thirdOption": "Isaac",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How many pieces of silver was Judas paid to betray Jesus?",
    "correctOption":"30",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "20",
    "secondOption": "30",
    "thirdOption": "40",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Only 2 persons in the Bible are reported as being 'taken up to Heaven' (instead of dying). One is Elijah. Who is the other?",
    "correctOption":"Enoch",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Enoch",
    "secondOption": "Elisha",
    "thirdOption": "Moses",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Moses died at age 120 and was buried in a valley of Moab. Who buried him?",
    "correctOption":"The Lord",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Joshua",
    "secondOption": "The Lord",
    "thirdOption": "Aaron",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How many years were the Israelites in bondage in Egypt?",
    "correctOption":"430",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "400",
    "secondOption": "470",
    "thirdOption": "430",
    "timer": 20,
    "answer":430
  },
  {
    "question":"When they heard of the adversity that had befallen Job, how many of his friends came to comfort him?",
    "correctOption":"3",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "1",
    "secondOption": "3",
    "thirdOption": "5",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who is the only woman mentioned in Paul’s letter to Philemon?",
    "correctOption":"Apphia",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Aggripa",
    "secondOption": "Apphia",
    "thirdOption": "Plilemon",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What part of the day did Christ embark on the boat from which He calmed the waters?",
    "correctOption":"Evening",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Afternoon",
    "secondOption": "Evening",
    "thirdOption": "Night",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"After his epiphany, how many years did Paul spend in Arabia before beginning his ministry?",
    "correctOption":"3",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "1",
    "secondOption": "2",
    "thirdOption": "3",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who was the father of John the Baptist?",
    "correctOption":"Zachariah",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Joseph",
    "secondOption": "Zachariah",
    "thirdOption": "John",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How many demons came out of Mary called Magdalene?",
    "correctOption":"7",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "5",
    "secondOption": "7",
    "thirdOption": "9",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who was the king of Israel when David slew Goliath?",
    "correctOption":"Saul",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Samuel",
    "secondOption": "Saul",
    "thirdOption": "Paul",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"To whom did God describe Job as a perfect and upright man?",
    "correctOption":"satan",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "His Friends",
    "secondOption": "satan",
    "thirdOption": "Job",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who said, “Silver and Gold have I none, but such as I have I give thee?”",
    "correctOption":"Peter",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Peter",
    "secondOption": "John",
    "thirdOption": "James",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"James, the brother of John, was the first Apostle martyred. How was he killed?",
    "correctOption":"With a sword",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "With a sword",
    "secondOption": "Crucifixion",
    "thirdOption": "Beheading",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How old (in years) was Abraham when his son Isaac was born?",
    "correctOption":"100",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "75",
    "secondOption": "99",
    "thirdOption": "100",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the title placed on Jesus’ cross?",
    "correctOption":"King of the Jews",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "King of the Jews",
    "secondOption": "Savior of the world",
    "thirdOption": "Leader of the people",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"When Jesus struggled with his cross, who was forced to bear it for him?",
    "correctOption":"Simon from Cyrene",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Mary Magdalene",
    "secondOption": "Simon from Cyrene",
    "thirdOption": "Joseph of Arimathea",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What body of water, other than the red sea, was parted in the Bible?",
    "correctOption":"Jordan river",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "None",
    "secondOption": "River nile",
    "thirdOption": "Jordan river",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the shortest chapter in the Bible?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Psalm 117",
    "secondOption": "Psalm 119",
    "thirdOption": "John 11: 35",
    "timer": 20,
    "correctOption":"Psalm 117"
  },
  {
    "question":"God parted the Red Sea so Moses and the Israelites could cross. What body of water did He part so Joshua and the Israelites could cross?",
    "correctOption":"Jordan river",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "None",
    "secondOption": "River nile",
    "thirdOption": "Jordan river",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"At Christ’s crucifixion darkness come over the whole land. How long did it last?",
    "correctOption":"3 hours",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "4 hours",
    "secondOption": "2 hours",
    "thirdOption": "3 hours",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"3 named women found Christ’s tomb open and empty: Mary Magdalene, Mary the mother of James, and _____?",
    "correctOption":"Joanna",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Joanna",
    "secondOption": "Mary",
    "thirdOption": "Monica",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question": "To which tribe of Israel did Moses belong?",
    "correctOption": "Levi",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Benjamin",
    "secondOption": "Levi",
    "thirdOption": "Joseph",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What relic did Moses remove from Egypt at the time of the Exodus?",
    "correctOption":"Bones of Joseph",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Bones of Joseph",
    "secondOption": "Bones of Jacob",
    "thirdOption": "Bones of Judah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How old was Abraham when he was circumcised?",
    "correctOption":"99",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "75",
    "secondOption": "99",
    "thirdOption": "100",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"After Christ’s triumphal entrance into Jerusalem and after visiting the temple, where did he spend the night?",
    "correctOption":"Bethany",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Bethany",
    "secondOption": "Galilee",
    "thirdOption": "Capernaum",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the tribes of Israel was prohibited from owning land in Canaan?",
    "correctOption":"Levites",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Levites",
    "secondOption": "Joseph",
    "thirdOption": "Judah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What city is called the City of David?",
    "correctOption":"Bethlehem",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Nazareth",
    "secondOption": "Israel",
    "thirdOption": "Bethlehem",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who ate honey out of a lion’s carcass?",
    "correctOption":"Samson",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Samuel",
    "secondOption": "Samson",
    "thirdOption": "Delilah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What famous city did Nebuchadnezzar rule?",
    "correctOption":"Babylon",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Judah",
    "secondOption": "Israel",
    "thirdOption": "Babylon",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who was Israel’s first high priest?",
    "correctOption":"Aaron",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Eli",
    "secondOption": "Aaron",
    "thirdOption": "Samuel",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who is the only woman whose age is mentioned in the Bible?",
    "correctOption":"Sarah",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Sarah",
    "secondOption": "Ruth",
    "thirdOption": "Naomi",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"When God finally let the Israelites enter the promised land of Canaan, how many nations had to be destroyed?",
    "correctOption":"7",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "6",
    "secondOption": "7",
    "thirdOption": "8",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"On the 7th day, how many times did Joshua’s army march around Jericho before the walls fell?",
    "correctOption":"7",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "6",
    "secondOption": "7",
    "thirdOption": "8",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Who did God describe as 'a blameless and upright man'?",
    "correctOption":"Job",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Samuel",
    "secondOption": "Job",
    "thirdOption": "Jesus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Aside from the Serpent, what other animal in the Old Testament spoke to humans?",
    "correctOption":"Donkey",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Dove",
    "secondOption": "Donkey",
    "thirdOption": "Horse",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Where is King David buried?",
    "correctOption":"City of David",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Land of Kings",
    "secondOption": "City of David",
    "thirdOption": "Land of Heroes",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How many Beatitudes are there?",
    "correctOption":"8",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "9",
    "secondOption": "10",
    "thirdOption": "8",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"How old (in years) was Noah when the flood was upon the earth?",
    "correctOption":"600",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "600",
    "secondOption": "700",
    "thirdOption": "800",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of Joseph’s (coat of many colors) 11 brothers said to his brothers not to kill Joseph but to cast him in a pit instead?",
    "correctOption":"Reuben",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Judah",
    "secondOption": "Reuben",
    "thirdOption": "Levi",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Paul said he would visit the Romans on this journey to which country?",
    "correctOption":"Spain",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Spain",
    "secondOption": "Italy",
    "thirdOption": "Antioch",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"After his epiphany on the road to Damascus, how many days was Saul without sight?",
    "correctOption":"3",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "4",
    "secondOption": "3",
    "thirdOption": "2",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"Where is Moses buried?",
    "correctOption":"Valley of Moab",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "Valley of Moab",
    "secondOption": "Hill of Moab",
    "thirdOption": "City of David",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"About how long was Christ on the cross before he said “My God, my God, why hast thou forsaken me?”",
    "correctOption":"9 hours",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "8 hours",
    "secondOption": "9 hours",
    "thirdOption": "10 hours",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"For refusing to worship a false god, Shadrach, Meshach, and Abednego were cast into a fiery furnace by King Nebuchadnezzar. How many times hotter than normal did the king order the furnace fire to be?",
    "correctOption":"7",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "firstOption": "4",
    "secondOption": "6",
    "thirdOption": "7",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 3rd plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption": "Lice",
    "secondOption": "Frogs",
    "firstOption": "Death of animals",
    "thirdOption": "Lice",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 4th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption": "Flies",
    "secondOption": "Boils",
    "firstOption": "Death of animals",
    "thirdOption": "Flies",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 5th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption": "Death of animals",
    "secondOption": "Boils",
    "firstOption": "Death of animals",
    "thirdOption": "Hail",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 6th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption": "Boils",
    "secondOption": "Boils",
    "firstOption": "Darkness",
    "thirdOption": "Hail",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 7th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption": "Hail",
    "secondOption": "Boils",
    "firstOption": "Darkness",
    "thirdOption": "Hail",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 8th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption":"Locusts",
    "secondOption": "Death of first-born son",
    "firstOption": "Darkness",
    "thirdOption": "Locusts",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 9th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption":"Darkness",
    "secondOption": "Death of first-born son",
    "firstOption": "Darkness",
    "thirdOption": "Locusts",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"

  },
  {
    "question":"What was the 10th plague God inflicted on Egypt?",
    "correctOption":"Death of first-born son",
    "secondOption": "Death of first-born son",
    "firstOption": "Darkness",
    "thirdOption": "Locusts",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many plagues did God inflict on Egypt?",
    "correctOption":"10",
    "secondOption": "8",
    "firstOption": "10",
    "thirdOption": "7",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which city was Jesus entering when Zacchaeus climbed a sycamore tree to see him?",
    "correctOption":"Jericho",
    "secondOption": "Galilee",
    "firstOption": "Jerusalem",
    "thirdOption": "Jericho",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Where did Cain go when he left Eden?",
    "correctOption":"Nod",
    "secondOption": "Galilee",
    "firstOption": "Jerusalem",
    "thirdOption": "Nod",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Name Jezebel’s husband.",
    "correctOption":"Ahab",
    "secondOption": "Ahaz",
    "firstOption": "Aman",
    "thirdOption": "Ahab",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"In the Bible, God is said to have physically written thrice – each time on a different surface. On what did his writing appear at the third instance?",
    "correctOption":"On the Wall",
    "secondOption": "In his cup",
    "firstOption": "On the floor",
    "thirdOption": "On the Wall",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Balaam was spoken to by which animal?",
    "correctOption":"Donkey",
    "secondOption": "Horse",
    "firstOption": "Sheep",
    "thirdOption": "Donkey",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What prophet issued ominous warning against people who took advantage of widows and the fatherless?",
    "correctOption":"Malachi",
    "secondOption": "Malachi",
    "firstOption": "Obadiah",
    "thirdOption": "Joel",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who did Mordecai refuse to bow down to?",
    "correctOption":"Haman",
    "secondOption": "Terah",
    "firstOption": "Tamah",
    "thirdOption": "Haman",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How old in years was Moses when he died?",
    "correctOption":"120",
    "secondOption": "129",
    "firstOption": "120",
    "thirdOption": "125",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How long was Daniel in the den of the lions?",
    "correctOption":"1 night",
    "secondOption": "1 night",
    "firstOption": "2 nights",
    "thirdOption": "3 nights",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What animal is mentioned most frequently in both the New and Old Testaments?",
    "correctOption":"Sheep",
    "secondOption": "Lamb",
    "firstOption": "Sheep",
    "thirdOption": "Dove",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"According to the Bible, how many pearly gates are there?",
    "correctOption":"12",
    "secondOption": "7",
    "firstOption": "10",
    "thirdOption": "12",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"In the Bible, which of the 4 horsemen of the Apocalypse rides a red horse?",
    "correctOption":"War",
    "secondOption": "Power",
    "firstOption": "War",
    "thirdOption": "Wisdom",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the colour of the horse which the 'War' horseman of the Apocalypse rides?",
    "correctOption":"Red",
    "secondOption": "Blue",
    "firstOption": "Red",
    "thirdOption": "Black",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"In the Bible, which of the 4 horsemen of the Apocalypse rides a pale/ashen horse?",
    "correctOption":"Death",
    "secondOption": "Death",
    "firstOption": "Heaven",
    "thirdOption": "Judgement",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What kind of tree did Zacchaeus climb to see Jesus enter Jericho?",
    "correctOption":"Sycamore",
    "secondOption": "Fig",
    "firstOption": "Sycamore",
    "thirdOption": "Palm tree",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who was able to decipher Nebuchadnezzar’s dreams?",
    "correctOption":"Daniel",
    "secondOption": "Hananiah",
    "firstOption": "Azariah",
    "thirdOption": "Daniel",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What king of Judah was stricken with leprosy?",
    "correctOption":"Uzziah",
    "secondOption": "Uzziah",
    "firstOption": "Saul",
    "thirdOption": "Jacob",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What occurred when Jonathan and his armor-bearer attacked the Philistines?",
    "correctOption":"Earthquake",
    "secondOption": "Tornado",
    "firstOption": "Earthquake",
    "thirdOption": "Famine",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who built the first altar?",
    "correctOption":"Noah",
    "secondOption": "Isaac",
    "firstOption": "Abraham",
    "thirdOption": "Noah",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many shekels did Abraham pay to buy the field of Machpelah?",
    "correctOption":"400",
    "secondOption": "350",
    "firstOption": "300",
    "thirdOption": "400",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"God is not mentioned in only 1 book of the Bible. Which one?",
    "correctOption":"Esther",
    "secondOption": "Esther",
    "firstOption": "Judith",
    "thirdOption": "Tobit",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"For how many pieces of silver was Joseph sold by his brothers to the Ishmaelites?",
    "correctOption":"20",
    "secondOption": "20",
    "firstOption": "40",
    "thirdOption": "30",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"The angel said to Mary that Jesus would 'reign over the house' of which Old Testament character?",
    "correctOption":"Jacob",
    "secondOption": "Moses",
    "firstOption": "Jacob",
    "thirdOption": "Isaac",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which prophet said, 'Out of Egypt have I called my son'?",
    "correctOption":"Hosea",
    "secondOption": "Hosea",
    "firstOption": "Malachi",
    "thirdOption": "Obadiah",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What type of tree did Jesus curse?",
    "correctOption":"Fig",
    "secondOption": "Mango",
    "firstOption": "Fig",
    "thirdOption": "Palm Tree",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"The fear of the Lord is the beginning of_________?",
    "correctOption":"Wisdom",
    "secondOption": "Understanding",
    "firstOption": "Knowledge",
    "thirdOption": "Wisdom",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What city did the Lord tell Jonah to preach against?",
    "correctOption":"Nineveh",
    "secondOption": "Nineveh",
    "firstOption": "Israel",
    "thirdOption": "Spain",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of these books (Philippians, Colossians, Galatians or Ephesians) come first in the Bible?",
    "correctOption":"Galatians",
    "secondOption": "Philippians",
    "firstOption": "Ephesians",
    "thirdOption": "Galatians",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many chapters does the book Hebrews have?",
    "correctOption":"13",
    "secondOption": "12",
    "firstOption": "13",
    "thirdOption": "14",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of the storm winds which can hit Crete?",
    "correctOption":"Euroklydon",
    "secondOption": "Euroklydon",
    "firstOption": "Eradon",
    "thirdOption": "Jordan",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"In which book of the bible to we read about Haman?",
    "correctOption":"Esther",
    "secondOption": "Esther",
    "firstOption": "Tobit",
    "thirdOption": "Ruth",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Name the only female judge mentioned in the Bible",
    "correctOption":"Deborah",
    "secondOption": "Esther",
    "firstOption": "Deborah",
    "thirdOption": "Judith",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Name the wife of King Agrippa, which Paul stood before on trial?",
    "correctOption":"Bernince",
    "secondOption": "Berdina",
    "firstOption": "Bernince",
    "thirdOption": "Judith",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How old did Enoch become?",
    "correctOption":"365",
    "secondOption": "365",
    "firstOption": "366",
    "thirdOption": "360",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What does Jahwe-Schammah mean?",
    "correctOption":"God himself",
    "secondOption": "God's Power",
    "firstOption": "God bless",
    "thirdOption": "God himself",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many more years did God add to King Hezekiah's life in response to the dying king's prayer?",
    "correctOption":"15",
    "secondOption": "19",
    "firstOption": "20",
    "thirdOption": "15",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What prophetess of the Lord did King Josiah of Judah consult?",
    "correctOption":"Huldah",
    "secondOption": "Ruth",
    "firstOption": "Judith",
    "thirdOption": "Huldah",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What ceremony did King Josiah reinstate that had not been celebrated by any of the previous kings of Israel or Judah?",
    "correctOption":"Passover",
    "secondOption": "Feast of the dead",
    "firstOption": "Feast of the Living",
    "thirdOption": "Passover",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Upon the return of the ark to Israel, what sacrifice did Samuel offer to the Lord?",
    "correctOption":"Suckling lamb",
    "secondOption": "Fire",
    "firstOption": "Ram",
    "thirdOption": "Suckling lamb",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Name Samuel's firstborn son",
    "correctOption":"Joel",
    "secondOption": "Jamis",
    "firstOption": "Joel",
    "thirdOption": "James",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was the name of king Saul's wife?",
    "correctOption":"Ahinoam",
    "secondOption": "Bathsheba",
    "firstOption": "Anjojah",
    "thirdOption": "Ahinoam",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is required for anyone to understand God's Word?",
    "correctOption":"Holy Spirit",
    "secondOption": "Love",
    "firstOption": "Jesus",
    "thirdOption": "Holy Spirit",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who did Paul say judged him?",
    "correctOption":"God",
    "secondOption": "God",
    "firstOption": "Festus",
    "thirdOption": "Ceasar",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who offered to pay money for the power to give the Holy Spirit?",
    "correctOption":"Simon",
    "secondOption": "Simeon",
    "firstOption": "Peter",
    "thirdOption": "Simon",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"When Jesus turned water into wine, he converted water that was in stone jars. What we’re these stone jars normally used for?",
    "correctOption":"Ceremonial washing",
    "secondOption": "Drinking",
    "firstOption": "Ceremonial washing",
    "thirdOption": "Bathing",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many books in the Bible have the name “John” in the title?",
    "correctOption":"4",
    "secondOption": "4",
    "firstOption": "2",
    "thirdOption": "3",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which book in the Bible has the shortest title?",
    "correctOption":"Job",
    "secondOption": "Ruth",
    "firstOption": "Mark",
    "thirdOption": "Job",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "question":"What were the names of the three sons of Noah in the order the Bible lists them in?",
    "correctOption":"Shem, Ham and Japheth",
    "secondOption": "Shem, Ham and Japheth",
    "firstOption": "Japheth, Shem and Ham",
    "thirdOption": "Ham, Shem and Japheth",
    "timer": 20,
    "quiz": "Bible"
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Saul",
    "firstOption": "David",
    "question": "Who was the first king of Israel?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Solomon",
    "thirdOption": "Saul",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Terah",
    "firstOption": "Terah",
    "question": "Who was the father of Abraham?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Tamah",
    "thirdOption": "Ramah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Good news",
    "firstOption": "Good news",
    "question": "What does the word gospel mean?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Word of God",
    "thirdOption": "Jesus Speaking",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Unknown",
    "firstOption": "Unknown",
    "question": "Who wrote the book of Hebrew?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Paul",
    "thirdOption": "John",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Jesus",
    "firstOption": "Peter",
    "question": "Who fed people with bread and fish in the Gospels?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Samuel",
    "thirdOption": "Jesus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Samson",
    "firstOption": "Peter",
    "question": "Who is the strongest man in the Bible?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Samson",
    "thirdOption": "Jesus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Judas",
    "firstOption": "Judas",
    "question": "Who betrayed Jesus?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Simon",
    "thirdOption": "Thomas",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Cain",
    "firstOption": "Adam",
    "question": "Who is the first to be born in the world?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Cain",
    "thirdOption": "Seth",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Anna",
    "firstOption": "Theresa",
    "question": "Who is the mother of Mary (mother of Jesus)?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Elizabeth",
    "thirdOption": "Anna",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "700",
    "firstOption": "700",
    "question": "How many wives did Solomon have?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "500",
    "thirdOption": "300",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Rebbecca",
    "firstOption": "Jezebel",
    "question": "Who is the first woman to wear earring in the Bible?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Rebbecca",
    "thirdOption": "Monica",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Three",
    "firstOption": "Three",
    "question": "How many days and nights did Jonah stay in the belly of the big fish?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Two",
    "thirdOption": "One",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Malachi",
    "firstOption": "Malachi",
    "question": "Who was the last prophet of the old testament?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Zephiniah",
    "thirdOption": "Habakkuk",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Methuselah",
    "firstOption": "Enoch",
    "question": "What is the name of the Oldest man in the Bible?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Methuselah",
    "thirdOption": "Adam",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "David",
    "firstOption": "Saul",
    "question": "Who killed Goliath?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "David",
    "thirdOption": "Solomon",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Egypt",
    "firstOption": "Ethiopia",
    "question": "From which country did Moses help the Israelites escape from?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Egypt",
    "thirdOption": "Jerusalem",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Green",
    "firstOption": "Red",
    "question": "What is the first color mentioned in the Bible?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Blue",
    "thirdOption": "Green",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Moses",
    "firstOption": "Moses",
    "question": "Who was given his name because he was drawn out of water?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Abraham",
    "thirdOption": "Aaron",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Benjamin",
    "firstOption": "Reuben",
    "question": "Which son did Jacob not send to Egypt for grain during famine?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Benjamin",
    "thirdOption": "Levi",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Rehab",
    "firstOption": "Rehab",
    "question": "Who hid two spies but denied their whereabouts?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Rebbecca",
    "thirdOption": "Sarah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Isaac",
    "firstOption": "Ishmael",
    "question": "Who's name means laughter?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Jacob",
    "thirdOption": "Isaac",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Jacob",
    "firstOption": "Esau",
    "question": "Who stole his brother's blessing?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Rebbecca",
    "thirdOption": "Jacob",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Tongue",
    "firstOption": "Tongue",
    "question": "What part of the body was referred to as a sword?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Teeth",
    "thirdOption": "Leg",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "40",
    "firstOption": "20",
    "question": "How many days and nights did Jesus fast?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "40",
    "thirdOption": "30",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "River Jordan",
    "firstOption": "Red sea",
    "question": "Where was Jesus baptised?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "River Jordan",
    "thirdOption": "River Nile",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "God will never flood the earth again?",
    "firstOption": "God will give him all his desires",
    "question": "What was God covenant with Noah?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "God will never flood the earth again?",
    "thirdOption": "God will make him rich",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Judges",
    "firstOption": "Judges",
    "question": "What book comes after Joshua?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Ruth",
    "thirdOption": "Samuel",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Leviticus",
    "firstOption": "Deuteronomy",
    "question": "What book comes after Exodus?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Leviticus",
    "thirdOption": "Numbers",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "James",
    "firstOption": "James",
    "question": "What book comes after Hebrew?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Peter",
    "thirdOption": "Jude",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Psalm 23",
    "firstOption": "Psalm 32",
    "question": "Which psalm has this phrase \"He makes me lie down in green pastures\"?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Psalm 23",
    "thirdOption": "Psalm 51",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "The Lord\u0027s prayer",
    "firstOption": "Divine Mercy",
    "question": "What is the name of the prayer Jesus taught his apostles?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Tantum Egro",
    "thirdOption": "The Lord\u0027s prayer",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Absalom",
    "firstOption": "Absalom",
    "question": "Which of David sons rebelled against him?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Andojah",
    "thirdOption": "Solomon",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Carpenter",
    "firstOption": "Plumber",
    "question": "What work did Jesus earthly father do?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Carpenter",
    "thirdOption": "Driver",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Hid it in the ground",
    "firstOption": "Invested with it",
    "question": "In one of Jesus prarables, the man who received one talent did what with it?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Dashed it out",
    "thirdOption": "Hid it in the ground",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Matthew",
    "firstOption": "Luke",
    "question": "Which New testament book has Jesus sermon on the mount?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Matthew",
    "thirdOption": "Mark",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Ishmael",
    "firstOption": "Isaac",
    "question": "What is the name of Hagar\u0027s son?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Ishmael",
    "thirdOption": "Solomon",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "God told him to strike a rock",
    "firstOption": "He prayed for rain ",
    "question": "When there was no water for the Israelites to drink in the wilderness, how did Moses provide water?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "He bought water ",
    "thirdOption": "God told him to strike a rock",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Crucifixion",
    "firstOption": "Amputation",
    "question": "What method did the Romans kill Jesus?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Beheading",
    "thirdOption": "Crucifixion",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Fifth",
    "firstOption": "Fifth",
    "question": "What day of creation did God create birds?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Sixth",
    "thirdOption": "Seventh",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Jethro",
    "firstOption": "Zachariah",
    "question": "What is the name of the priest of Midian (Moses father in-law)?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Jethro",
    "thirdOption": "Hurt",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Built a golden calf",
    "firstOption": "Prayed",
    "question": "What did the Israelites do when Moses was receiving the ten commandments?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Built a golden calf",
    "thirdOption": "Fasted",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Pentecost",
    "firstOption": "Passover",
    "question": "On what day did the disciples of Christ receive the holy spirit and spoke in tongues?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Prayer",
    "thirdOption": "Pentecost",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Locusts and Wild Honey",
    "firstOption": "Rat meat",
    "question": "What type of insect did John the Baptist eat in the desert? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Locusts and Wild Honey",
    "thirdOption": "Milk",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Peter and Andrew",
    "firstOption": "Peter and Andrew",
    "question": "Who were the first apostles called to follow Jesus?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "James and John",
    "thirdOption": "Matthew and Mark",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "5000",
    "firstOption": "3000",
    "question": "How many people did Jesus feed with five loaves of bread and two fish? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "4500",
    "thirdOption": "5000",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Wisdom",
    "firstOption": "Wisdom",
    "question": "What did King Solomon ask God to give him?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Knowledge",
    "thirdOption": "Understanding",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Simeon",
    "firstOption": "Anna",
    "question": "Who recognized Jesus as the Messiah when he was presented at the Temple as a baby? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Simeon",
    "thirdOption": "Mary",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Joseph of Arimathea",
    "firstOption": "Joseph of Arimathea",
    "question": "Who asked Pilate for Jesus’ body after the crucifixion? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Barnabbas",
    "thirdOption": "Nicodemus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Malta",
    "firstOption": "Patmos",
    "question": "Paul was shipwrecked on what island? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Sinai",
    "thirdOption": "Malta",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "2 John",
    "firstOption": "2 John",
    "question": "What is the shortest book in the New Testament? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "1 John",
    "thirdOption": "3 John",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Damascus",
    "firstOption": "Malta",
    "question": "To what city was Saul traveling when he encountered a great and blinding light? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Damascus",
    "thirdOption": "Africa",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Priest",
    "firstOption": "Priest",
    "question": "Who was the first person to come upon the injured man in the parable of the Good Samaritan? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Levite",
    "thirdOption": "Samaritan",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Christ\u0027s",
    "firstOption": "God",
    "question": "Whose example does Paul say Christians should follow in Chapter 5 of Ephesians? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "His",
    "thirdOption": "Christ\u0027s",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "12",
    "firstOption": "11",
    "question": "After Jesus fed 5,000+ people with two fish and five loaves of bread, how many baskets were left over? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "12",
    "thirdOption": "13",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Love",
    "firstOption": "Hope",
    "question": "What does Paul say may “abound more and more in knowledge and in all judgment?”",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Faith",
    "thirdOption": "Love",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Benjamin",
    "firstOption": "Benjamin",
    "question": "What tribe is Paul from? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Reuben",
    "thirdOption": "Levi",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Jesse",
    "firstOption": "Isaiah",
    "question": "Who is the father of David?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Jesse",
    "thirdOption": "Paul",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Those who hunger and thirst for righteousness",
    "firstOption": "The poor",
    "question": "According to the Beatitudes who will be filled? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Those who hunger and thirst for righteousness",
    "thirdOption": "Those who morn",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Fisherman",
    "firstOption": "Hunter",
    "question": "What does Simon Peter do for a living before he becomes an apostle? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Carpenter",
    "thirdOption": "Fisherman",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "From the angel Gabriel",
    "firstOption": "From the angel Gabriel",
    "question": "In the Gospel of Mark, how does the Virgin Mary learn of her pregnancy? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "From Angel Raphael",
    "thirdOption": "From Simeon",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Saul",
    "firstOption": "Paul",
    "question": "By what name is Paul of Tarsus known before he begins his missionary activity? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Saul",
    "thirdOption": "Bar Jesus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Caiphas",
    "firstOption": "Caiphas",
    "question": "Who is the high priest of Jerusalem who put Jesus on trial? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Herod",
    "thirdOption": "Pilate",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Thomas",
    "firstOption": "Matthew",
    "question": "In the Gospel According to John, which of the apostles doubts Jesus’s resurrection until he sees Jesus with his own eyes? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "John",
    "thirdOption": "Thomas",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "He kisses him",
    "firstOption": "He Points him",
    "question": "How does Judas signal Jesus’s identity to the Roman officials? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "He hugs him",
    "thirdOption": "He kisses him",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Jesus suffering and death",
    "firstOption": "Jesus’s entry into Jerusalem before his death",
    "question": "When Christians observe Palm Sunday, what biblical narrative are they celebrating? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Jesus suffering and death",
    "thirdOption": "Jesus trial",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "The Gospels",
    "firstOption": "Septuagint",
    "question": "What is the common name given to the first four books of the New Testament?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "The Gospels",
    "thirdOption": "The Deuterocanonicals",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Luke",
    "firstOption": "Mark",
    "question": "Who wrote the Acts of the apostles?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Luke",
    "thirdOption": "John",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Ham",
    "firstOption": "Ram",
    "question": "Who is the first person to see his father nakedness?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Ham",
    "thirdOption": "Ramma",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "37",
    "firstOption": "37",
    "question": "Which wood has been used by Noah to build the ark?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "38",
    "thirdOption": "39",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Death",
    "firstOption": "Death",
    "question": "Who sat on the pale Horse of Revelation 6?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "The King",
    "thirdOption": "Sin",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "They sold Him",
    "firstOption": "They killed him",
    "question": "What did Joseph\u0027s brothers do to get rid of him?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "They sold Him",
    "thirdOption": "They buried him",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "James",
    "firstOption": "Levi",
    "question": "Name a son of Zebedee?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Simon",
    "thirdOption": "James",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Love them and Pray for them",
    "firstOption": "Preach to them",
    "question": "According to Jesus, how do we treat our Enemies?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Avoid them",
    "thirdOption": "Love them and Pray for them",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Walking on water",
    "firstOption": "Raising Lazarus from dead",
    "question": "What miracle did Jesus perform when he said \"It is I, do not he afraid\"?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Walking on water",
    "thirdOption": "Turning water into wine",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Nehimiah",
    "firstOption": "Psalms",
    "question": "What book comes after Ezra?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Job",
    "thirdOption": "Nehimiah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "1 Chronicles",
    "firstOption": "Ezra",
    "question": "What book comes after 2 Kings?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "1 Samuel",
    "thirdOption": "1 Chronicles",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "In-law",
    "firstOption": "Sister",
    "question": "How is Ruth related to Naomi?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Neighbor",
    "thirdOption": "In-law",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Tree of Knowledge of Good and Evil",
    "firstOption": "Tree of destruction",
    "question": "Of what, specifically was not allowed to eat in the Garden of Eden?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Tree of Knowledge of Good and Evil",
    "thirdOption": "The tree of Wisdom",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Washed their feet",
    "firstOption": "Washed their feet",
    "question": "What did Jesus do to each of the disciples during the Last Supper? ",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Thanked them for their kindness",
    "thirdOption": "Prayed for them",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Take no thought of it",
    "firstOption": "Take no thought of it",
    "question": "What did Jesus say about tomorrow in him sermon on the mount?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "It will end",
    "thirdOption": "Have good plans for tomorrow",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Commanded the Spirit to leave her.",
    "firstOption": "Commanded the Spirit to leave her.",
    "question": "What did Paul do to the soothsayer that made her masters unhappy?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Cursed the spirit",
    "thirdOption": "Praised the spirit ",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Eve",
    "firstOption": "Sarah",
    "question": "Who is the first Mother mentioned in the Bible?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Jezebel",
    "thirdOption": "Eve",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Gold",
    "firstOption": "Gold",
    "question": "In the New Jerusalem described in Revelation, what are the twelve gates made from?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Bronze",
    "thirdOption": "Pearl",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Light of the world",
    "firstOption": "Immanuel",
    "question": "Which one of these is not a title of Jesus Christ?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Holy One of Israel",
    "thirdOption": "Light of the world",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Patmos",
    "firstOption": "Malta",
    "question": "On what island was John when he was given the vision of Revelation?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Patmos",
    "thirdOption": "Rome",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Miletus",
    "firstOption": "Philadelphia",
    "question": "Which of these is not one of the churches of Asia Minor?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Ephesus",
    "thirdOption": "Miletus",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "7",
    "firstOption": "4",
    "question": "How many churches of Asia Minor were there?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "11",
    "thirdOption": "7",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Adam",
    "firstOption": "Adam",
    "question": "Who is the father of Seth?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Cain",
    "thirdOption": "Enoch",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "2 years",
    "firstOption": "2 years",
    "question": "During Paul\u0027s third missionary journey, roughly for how long did he minister in the school of Tyrannus at Ephesus?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "4 years",
    "thirdOption": "1 year",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Philippi",
    "firstOption": "Paphos",
    "question": "Paul and Silas were imprisoned during the second missionary journey, but in what city did this happen?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Philippi",
    "thirdOption": "Antioch",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Barnabas",
    "firstOption": "Barnabas",
    "question": "Who went with Paul on his first missionary journey?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Mark",
    "thirdOption": "Luke",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "40",
    "firstOption": "20",
    "question": "For how many days did Jesus appear to his disciples after his resurrection?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "30",
    "thirdOption": "40",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Golgotha",
    "firstOption": "Gethsemane",
    "question": "Where was Jesus crucified?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Golgotha",
    "thirdOption": "Mount of Olives",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Dipped a piece of bread and passed it to him",
    "firstOption": "Washed his feet",
    "question": "How did Jesus reveal the one who would betray him?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Dipped a piece of bread and passed it to him",
    "thirdOption": "Poured out the wine and passed it to him",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Moses and Elijah",
    "firstOption": "James and John",
    "question": "Which two Old Testament characters appeared with Jesus at the transfiguration?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Peter and Andrew",
    "thirdOption": "Moses and Elijah",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Zacchaeus",
    "firstOption": "Zacchaeus",
    "question": "Who was the tax collector that climbed up a tree so he could see Jesus?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Matthew",
    "thirdOption": "Luke",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "Herod the Great",
    "firstOption": "Herod Phillip",
    "question": "Who was the king of Judea at the time of Jesus\u0027 birth?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "Herod the Great",
    "thirdOption": "Herod Agrippa I",
    "timer": 20
  },
  {
    "correctOption": "27",
    "firstOption": "26",
    "question": "How many books are there in the New Testament?",
    "quiz": "Bible",
    "secondOption": "66",
    "thirdOption": "27",
    "timer": 20
  }
]